I'd just like a trim.
我只想稍微修剪一下.
Whatever you want.
随你所愿.
So what do you think of him?
So 你认为他怎么样?
-Kevin?  -Who do you think?
-Kevin?  -你认为还有谁?
I'm not sure.I like the way he talks.
我不确定. 我喜欢他谈话的方式.
I like the way he smiles.
我喜欢他笑的样子,
I like the way he looks.
我喜欢他的长相.
So you like him.
So 你喜欢他.
He makes me laugh all the time.
他总是让我发笑.
He's very sociable.
他非常善于交际.
He has a lot of confidence.
他很有自信.
He can deal with any situation.
他能应对任何情况.
He's really smart too,isn't he?
他也很聪明, 对不对?
Didn't you say he used to be a physicist?
你以前不是说他过去是位物理学家吗?
Oh.That's a long story.
Oh. 那是个长故事.
But he is pretty smart.
不过他相当聪明.
How old is he?
他多大?
My age.
我的年纪.
And he's had all these interesting experiences,
并且他有很多有趣的经历,
because he's so well-traveled.
因为他去过很多地方.
How's that?
怎么样?
Great.He's really wonderful.
Great. 他确实很出色.
You know,for someone who's not sure,
你知道, 对于一个不确定的人,
you sound pretty sure.
你听起来很确定.
You see Steven,your haircuts always clear my mind.
你看 Steven, 你的理发总是让我头脑清醒.